export const DiscursiveQuestions = {
    q1: {
        numberQuestion: "01",
        title: "Título pergunta número 1",
        answer: "Resposta 1",
    },
    q2: {
        numberQuestion: "02",
        title: "Título pergunta número 2",
        answer: "Resposta 2",
    },
    q3: {
        numberQuestion: "03",
        title: "Título pergunta número 3",
        answer: "Resposta 3",
    },
    q4: {
        numberQuestion: "04",
        title: "Título pergunta número 4",
        answer: "Resposta 4",
    },
    q5: {
        numberQuestion: "05",
        title: "Título pergunta número 5",
        answer: "Resposta 5",
    },
    q6: {
        numberQuestion: "06",
        title: "Título pergunta número 6",
        answer: "Resposta 6",
    },
    q7: {
        numberQuestion: "07",
        title: "Título pergunta número 7",
        answer: "Resposta 7",
    },
    q8: {
        numberQuestion: "08",
        title: "Título pergunta número 8",
        answer: "Resposta 8",
    },
    q9: {
        numberQuestion: "09",
        title: "Título pergunta número 9",
        answer: "Resposta 9",
    },
    q10: {
        numberQuestion: "10",
        title: "Título pergunta número 10",
        answer: "Resposta 10",
    },
}